Guide to the Harry Randall: Fifteenth International Brigade Films and Photographs ALBA.PHOTO.011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series C: Group Portraits, September 1937-August 1938.
  - Photo Unit #: C002 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner, group 2, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0694)
  - Photo Unit #: C003 Lincoln-Washington Battalion eating, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0693)
  - Photo Unit #: C004 Two Armenians, Lincoln-Washington, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0695)
  - Photo Unit #: C005 [?] Neilson (l.) and Kenneth Brown, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-1316)
  - Photo Unit #: C006 G. Dilich (l.) and Kenneth Brown, Lincoln-Washington, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0696)
  - Photo Unit #: C007 First aid men of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0697)
  - Photo Unit #: C008 Lincoln-Washington kitchen, Senes, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0698)
  - Photo Unit #: C009 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company, rain, Senes, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0699)
  - Photo Unit #: C010 Lincoln-Washington kitchen, Senes, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0700)
  - Photo Unit #: C011 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company pay day, Senes, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0701)
  - Photo Unit #: C012 [?] Gordon (l.) and John Robinson, Asst. Political Commissar of 15th Brigade, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0702)
  - Photo Unit #: C013 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company and Sec. 1, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0703)
  - Photo Unit #: C014 Joe Bianca, Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company, Sec. 2, Crew 3, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0704)
  - Photo Unit #: C015 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company Sec. 2, Crew 4, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0705)
  - Photo Unit #: C016 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company Sec. 1, Crew 2, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0706)
  - Photo Unit #: C017 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company Sec. 3, Crew 5, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0707)
  - Photo Unit #: C018 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company Sec. 3, Crew 6 (Spanish), Sep 1937 (Item 11-0708)
  - Photo Unit #: C020 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gu officers: Milton Wolff, Mike Pappas, Zip Kachinski (Item 11-1820)
  - Photo Unit #: C021 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Runners, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0709)
  - Photo Unit #: C022 Lincoln-Washington Machine-Gunner Company post office, Almuchel: [?] Brown, Battalion Postman, [?] Wilson, Brigade Postman, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0710)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/23)
  - Photo Unit #: C023 John Robinson (l.) and Captain Leonard Lamb, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0711)
  - Photo Unit #: C024 John Robinson (l.), Philip Detro and Captain Leonard Lamb, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0712)
  - Photo Unit #: C025 Philip Detro (l.) and Captiain Leonard Lamb, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0713)
  - Photo Unit #: C026 Carl Geiser (l.), Philip Detro and Captain Leonard Lamb, Lincoln-Washington, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0714)
  - Photo Unit #: C027 Lincoln-Washington Battalion Staff, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0715)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/4)
  - Photo Unit #: C028 Lincoln-Washington ambulance and medical personnel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-1817)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/17)
  - Photo Unit #: C029 Officers of Company 1, 24th Battalion, undated (Item 11-1788)
    (Moscow Number: 5/183/37)
  - Photo Unit #: C030 Lieutenant Commander Abad Garcia of the 24th Battalion (left); José María Varela, Political Commissar of the 24th Battalion (right), Sep 1937 (Item 11-1787)
    (Moscow Number: 5/183/36)
  - Photo Unit #: C032 Officers and Political Delegates of Company 2, 24th Battalion, Sep 1937 (Item 11-1790)
    (Moscow Number: 5/183/42)
  - Photo Unit #: C033 Comrades of 24th Battalion who captured Fascist Commander Santapu and Lieutenant Colonel San Martin, Sep 1937 (Item 11-1789)
    (Moscow Number: 5/183/41)
  - Photo Unit #: C035 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Sep 1937 (Item 11-1885)
  - Photo Unit #: C037 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0716)
  - Photo Unit #: C038 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0717)
  - Photo Unit #: C039 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0718)
  - Photo Unit #: C040 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0719)
  - Photo Unit #: C041 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Sep 1937 (Item 11-1886)
  - Photo Unit #: C042 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0720)
  - Photo Unit #: C043 Harry Poll speaking at meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0721)
    (Moscow Number: 5/183/40)
  - Photo Unit #: C044 Meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0722)
  - Photo Unit #: C045 David Doran addressing meeting of American Company of 24th Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0723)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/27)
  - Photo Unit #: C050 M. Constant [?] (l.) and G.R. Dias [?], Ambite, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0724)
  - Photo Unit #: C051 15th Brigade Armorers, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0976)
  - Photo Unit #: C052 15th Brigade Armorers, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0725)
  - Photo Unit #: C056 Joseph Dougher (l.) and Carl Bradley, Captain of 24th Battalion, American Company, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0726)
  - Photo Unit #: C058 Pat Reid (l.) and Harry Fisher, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0727)
  - Photo Unit #: C059 Joseph Dougher, Commissar, MacKenzie-Papineau, Company 3 (l.), Albert (Abe) Harris, Brigade Intendencia, and Wally Sabatini, Political Commissar, MacKenzie-Papineau, Company 3, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0728)
  - Photo Unit #: C060 New York University Volunteers: Leonard B. Levenson, Paul Sigel, Emanuel Mandel, Elkan Wendkos, ?; and Paul MacEachron (Oberlin College), at Azaila, Spain, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0729)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/3)
  - Photo Unit #: C061 Carl Bradley (l.) and Radomir Smrcka, 15th Brigade Information Service, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0730)
  - Photo Unit #: C063 Robert Thompson, Battalion Commander of 15th International Brigade, MacKenzie-Papineau (l.), Philip Detro of Lincoln-Washington, [?] Garcia 24th, [?] O'Dair (British) and [?] Aguila 24th Battalion, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0731)
  - Photo Unit #: C064 Rollin Dart (l.), Captain of Brigade staff, and David Doran, Oct 1937 (Item 11-1317)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/32)
  - Photo Unit #: C067 Officers of British anti-tank [unit:] Bill Alexander (left) P. D., Hugh Slater, [?], Oct 1937 (Item 11-1318)
  - Photo Unit #: C068 Anti-Tank Unit leaders, undated (Item 11-1319)
  - Photo Unit #: C071 15th Brigade Transmissions at Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0732)
  - Photo Unit #: C072 15th Brigade Transmissions at Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0733)
  - Photo Unit #: C074 Officers of Lincoln-Washington Company 3, Com. Sancha [?], Murielo [?], and Florentino Alejo Ortiz [?], Political Commissar, Almuchel, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0734)
  - Photo Unit #: C075 Cubans in Lincoln-Washington, Company 3, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0735)
  - Photo Unit #: C076 Lincoln-Washington Section 3, Company 3, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0736)
  - Photo Unit #: C079 Greeks in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0737)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/28)
  - Photo Unit #: C080 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 3, Sec. 3, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0738)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/3)
  - Photo Unit #: C081 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 3, Sec. 4, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0739)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/6)
  - Photo Unit #: C082 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 3 officers (5) Mouton, (6) William Miller, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0740)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/29)
  - Photo Unit #: C083 Spanish in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 3, Section 3, Almuchel; [nine soldiers], Sep 1937 (Item 11-1819)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/26)
  - Photo Unit #: C084 Spanish comrades of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-1822)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/40)
  - Photo Unit #: C085 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 1, Group 1, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0741)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/18)
  - Photo Unit #: C086 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 3, Group 1, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0742)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/24)
  - Photo Unit #: C087 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 2, Group 1, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0743)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/21)
  - Photo Unit #: C088 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 1, Group 2, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0744)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/22)
  - Photo Unit #: C090 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 2, Group 3, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0745)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/9)
  - Photo Unit #: C091 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Section 3, Group 2, Almuchel; [three soldiers with a machine gun], Sep 1937 (Item 11-1818)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/19)
  - Photo Unit #: C092 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 3, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0746)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/41)
  - Photo Unit #: C093 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 3, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0747)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/10)
  - Photo Unit #: C094 Officers, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0748)
  - Photo Unit #: C095 Officers and Company Staff, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0749)
  - Photo Unit #: C096 Officers and Company Staff, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0750)
  - Photo Unit #: C097 Kenneth Brown, Company 1 Political Commissar and Political Delegate, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0977)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/7)
  - Photo Unit #: C098 Scouts of the Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Almuchel, [four soldiers], Sep 1937 (Item 11-1814)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/8)
  - Photo Unit #: C099 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sec. 1, Group 3, Almuchel, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0751)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/37)
  - Photo Unit #: C100 Comrades from Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Company 1, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0752)
  - Photo Unit #: C101 David Doran (c.), Political Commissar, 15th Brigade, John Robinson (r.), Asst. Political Commissar, 15th Brigade, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0753)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/31)
  - Photo Unit #: C103 Group at 15th International Brigade Estado Mayor [Headquarters] at Ambite, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0754)
  - Photo Unit #: C104 Group at waterbarrel: Ivan Rujevcic [alias John Gerlach], Robert Merriman, Rollin Dart, David Doran and John Robinson (second from l.-r.), Sep 1937 (Item 11-0755)
  - Photo Unit #: C105 Ivan Rujevcic [alias John Gerlach] (l.) and David Doran, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0756)
  - Photo Unit #: C107 David Doran (l.), Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic and Captain Radomir Smrcka, Ambite, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0978)
  - Photo Unit #: C108 Harry Pollitt, David Doran, Radomir Smercka, Vladimir Copic, Major Germina Galleani, "Max," Ambite, Nov 1937 (Item 11-1759)
    (Moscow Number: 5/177/29)
  - Photo Unit #: C109 David Doran, Elias Begelman, Vladimir Copic, "Max", Major Germina Galleani, Ambite, Nov 1937 (Item 11-1758)
    Available Formats: Moscow negative
    (Moscow Number: 5/177/17)
  - Photo Unit #: C110 Umberto Galliani, Garibaldi Brigade [12th], undated (Item 11-1321)
  - Photo Unit #: C111 Elias Begelman, Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, [?], Galleani, Dunbar at Ambite, Nov 1937 (Item 11-1322)
  - Photo Unit #: C114 Robert Merriman, [?] and Vladimir Copic, Sep 1937 (Item 11-0757)
    (Moscow Number: 5/177/31)
  - Photo Unit #: C120 British Anti-tank and kitchen, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0063)
  - Photo Unit #: C126 Abraham Eisenberg and [?] Shapiro (deserter), Nov 1937 (Item 11-0979)
  - Photo Unit #: C128 James Bourne (l.) and David Doran, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0758)
  - Photo Unit #: C129 Frank Ryan (l.) and John Robinson, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0759)
  - Photo Unit #: C130 David Doran (l.) and John Robinson, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0760)
  - Photo Unit #: C131 Estado Mayor [Headquarters] staff at Senes, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0761)
  - Photo Unit #: C134 British Battalion, F. Doysle [?], Company 3 Political Commissar; F. Madigan [?], Company 3 Commander, Senes, Oct 1937 (Item 11-1794)
    (Moscow Number: 5/184/5)
  - Photo Unit #: C135 British Battalion Serano Com. [?] Company 4, Senes, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0980)
  - Photo Unit #: C137 Lincoln-Washington Battalion, kitchen [serving food] [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Oct 1937 (Item 11-1887)
  - Photo Unit #: C139 Kitchen staff, Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0762)
  - Photo Unit #: C140 Ivan Rujevcic (l.) and Rollin Dart, Quinto, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0763)
  - Photo Unit #: C141 M[?] Safir (l.) and David Doran at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0764)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/25)
  - Photo Unit #: C143 José María Mateo Sastre, Asst. Commissar of 15th Brigade, and David Doran, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0765)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/29)
  - Photo Unit #: C144 Albert Chisholm (l.) and George Waters, Oct 1937 (Item 11-1323)
  - Photo Unit #: C145 Doctor Mark Straus (l.) and Major Robert Merriman at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0766)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/1)
  - Photo Unit #: C146 Spanish solidiers of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion at rest in Quinto after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937 (Item 11-1832)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/16)
  - Photo Unit #: C147 Ukranians of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion at rest after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937 (Item 11-1835)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/24)
  - Photo Unit #: C148 Machine-Gunner Company of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0767)
  - Photo Unit #: C149 [?] (l.) and Eugene Nolte after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0768)
  - Photo Unit #: C150 MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937 (Item 11-1836)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/25)
  - Photo Unit #: C151 Spaniards of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion at rest after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937 (Item 11-1840)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/33)
  - Photo Unit #: C152 [?] (l.), [?] and Jack Thomas after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0769)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/17)
  - Photo Unit #: C155 15th Brigade cyclists Abraham Irving Halpern, Robert Minor and John Burning, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0981)
  - Photo Unit #: C156 Brigade Scouts at Quinto after Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937 (Item 11-1782)
    (Moscow Number: 5/181/15)
  - Photo Unit #: C158 Robert Minor (l.), [?] and [?] at Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Quinto, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0770)
    (Moscow Number: 5/189/13)
  - Photo Unit #: C160 British Battalion Medical Corps, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0256)
  - Photo Unit #: C161 Vladimir Copic and Robert Merriman, Estado Mayor [Headquarters], Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0258)
  - Photo Unit #: C162 Robert Merriman and Rollin Dart, Fuentes de Ebro, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0257)
  - Photo Unit #: C168 Brigade Scouts, Ambite, Captain Radomir Smrcka in charge, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0982)
  - Photo Unit #: C169 Brigade Scouts, Ambite, Captain Radomir Smrcka in charge, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0983)
  - Photo Unit #: C172 Eugene Poling (l.) and "Doc" James Hill, both from Oklahoma and received citations, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0984)
  - Photo Unit #: C190 Colin Charles "Doc" Bradsworth and practicantes of the MacKenzie-Papineau, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0985)
  - Photo Unit #: C193 First-aid class at MacKenzie-Papineau, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0986)
  - Photo Unit #: C198 Group {Transmiciones?}; Louis Stoloff, at right, front row, undated (Item 11-0986A)
  - Photo Unit #: C199 Brigade Topographers Albert Kohn (l.), Hans Gutman and Doug [Orville Douglas] Taylor, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0987)
  - Photo Unit #: C200 Herman "Gabby" Klein (l.) and Louis Eider at Ambite, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0988)
  - Photo Unit #: C201[?] Lincoln-Washington machine-gun officers: Milton Wolff, Mike Pappas, Zip Kachinski, and three others, undated (Item 11-1820)
    (Moscow Number: 5/185/31)
  - Photo Unit #: C202 David Doran (l.), Marion Merriman, Major Robert Merriman at Ambite, Nov 1937 (Item 11-1324)
  - Photo Unit #: C204 Ernest Kozlowski, James Bourne, Ambite, Nov 1937 (Item 11-0989)
  - Photo Unit #: C215 Wally Sabatini (standing), Political Commissar, Company 3, MacKenzie-Papineau and Egan Schmidt, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0771)
  - Photo Unit #: C223 British Battalion, (1) J.L. Walker (2), A. MacIntosh (3), F. West (4) F. O'Brien--"Hammersmith Boys", Dec 1937 (Item 11-1325)
  - Photo Unit #: C228 [?] Reis, Com. David (Red) Drummond, Political Commissar, Machine-Gunner Company, Lincoln-Washington, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0772)
  - Photo Unit #: C229 [?] (l.), John Robinson and Langston Hughes, Fuentes, Oct 1937 (Item 11-0773)
  - Photo Unit #: C234 Brigade Machine-Gunner Company, Ambite, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0990)
  - Photo Unit #: C236 Transmiciones [Transmissions] of 15th Brigade, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0991)
  - Photo Unit #: C237 Trans. [?] [Isador] Frank Barcena and Patrick Read, Ambite, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0992)
  - Photo Unit #: C238 Intendencia, Mondejar, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0993)
  - Photo Unit #: C242 Rifle team of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0994)
  - Photo Unit #: C247 Otto Reeves (l.) and Frank Alexander of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0995)
  - Photo Unit #: C251 Captain Nilo Makela, MacKenzie-Papineau, and Captain Edward Cecil Smith, Dec 1937 (Item 11-1326)
  - Photo Unit #: C252 Group of MacKenzie-Papineau [with banner], Dec 1937 (Item 11-1327)
  - Photo Unit #: C253 Captain Alfredo Balsa, José María Varela, Political Commissar of 24th Battalion, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0996)
  - Photo Unit #: C255 David Doran, José María Varela at Larance, Captain Alfredo Balsa, John Gates, Political Commissar, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0997)
  - Photo Unit #: C257 American and Spaniards in 24th [Brigade?] Machine-Gunner Company, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0998)
  - Photo Unit #: C263 15th Brigade Hospital Corps at Alcorisa, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0999)
  - Photo Unit #: C264 Ambulance drivers of the 15th Brigade [in front of ambulance] [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Dec 1937 (Item 11-1888)
  - Photo Unit #: C265 Nurses of 15th Brigade, Dec 1937 (Item 11-1000)
  - Photo Unit #: C266 Ambulance drivers [of the 15th Brigade in front of Illinois State International Labor Defense ambulance] [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Dec 1937 (Item 11-1889)
  - Photo Unit #: C267 Doctors of the 15th Brigade [in front of Artists Union ambulance] [copy negative; transferred from the Victor Berch Papers, ALBA 080], Dec 1937 (Item 11-1890)
  - Photo Unit #: C268 Doctor Edward Barsky and Doctor [?], Dec 1937 (Item 11-1001)
  - Photo Unit #: C269 Lumbermen from Northwest: John Givulinovich and Wilfred "Idaho" Chapin, Dec 1937 (Item 11-1002)
  - Photo Unit #: C270 English kitchen at Alcaniz, Dec 1937 (Item 11-1003)
  - Photo Unit #: C276 Group of Servicio Sanidad [Health] of Lincoln-Washington, Dec 1937 (Item 11-1004)
  - Photo Unit #: C277 [?] and Harry Noble, Dec 1937 (Item 11-1005)
  - Photo Unit #: C279 Sound truck, R. Karman [?] and C. Silverman [?], Dec 1937 (Item 11-1006)
  - Photo Unit #: C281 Nathan Weisenfeld [alias Neil Wesson], Major Robert Merriman, Captain Alfredo Balsa, Dec 1937 (Item 11-1328)
  - Photo Unit #: C285 Train group going from Ambite to Alcaniz, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0774)
  - Photo Unit #: C287 Train group going from Ambite to Alcaniz, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0775)
  - Photo Unit #: C288 Chauffeurs, 15th British [?], Auto Park, Dec 1937 (Item 11-1007)
  - Photo Unit #: C289 Three Carbonell brothers, Pablo, Victor, Jorge, Dec 1937 (Item 11-1008)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/23)
  - Photo Unit #: C290 Chauffeurs, "Dusty" Miller, Kaye Alexander, Dec 1937 (Item 11-1009)
  - Photo Unit #: C293 Louis Secundy, Abraham Lewis, Dec 1937 (Item 11-1010)
  - Photo Unit #: C298 John Gates (l.), Political Commissar, International Brigade base, Captain Robert Thompson, MacKenzie-Papineau and David Doran, Political Commissar, 15th Brigade, Ambite, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0776)
  - Photo Unit #: C299 David Doran, Lieutenant Harry Poll, Lieutenant Colonel Vladimir Copic, General Walter [alias of Karol Swierczewski], Dec 1937 (Item 11-0777)
  - Photo Unit #: C303 Louis Secundy, Chief of Auto Park, 15th International Brigade, Dec 1937 (Item 11-0778)
  - Photo Unit #: C304 [?], Joe Taylor and [?], Brigade Scouts, Dec 1937 (Item 11-1329)
  - Photo Unit #: C306 At Argente, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1011)
  - Photo Unit #: C307 [?], [?] and Claude Pringle, Dec 1937 (Item 11-1012)
  - Photo Unit #: C310 Group of Brigade Commissariat, Argente, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1013)
  - Photo Unit #: C317 At front, E. [?] Teruel, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1014)
  - Photo Unit #: C319 At Estado Mayor [Headquarters] at Teruel Front, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1015)
  - Photo Unit #: C320 At MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion near [?], Jan 1938 (Item 11-1016)
  - Photo Unit #: C327 Cubans in the 24th Brigade, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1017)
  - Photo Unit #: C330 Couriers of 15th Brigade, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1018)
  - Photo Unit #: C331 Motor cyclists of 15th Brigade, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1019)
  - Photo Unit #: C333 Jesse Wallach, Samuel Romer, Eugene Nolte of MacKenzie-Papineau Battalion, Jan 1938 (Item 11-1020)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/29)
  - Photo Unit #: C337 In Teruel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0779)
  - Photo Unit #: C338 In Teruel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0780)
  - Photo Unit #: C345 Robert Merriman, Earl Browder, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0781)
  - Photo Unit #: C346 Earl Browder, Vladimir Copic, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0782)
  - Photo Unit #: C348 Earl Browder and officers of the 15th International Brigade, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0783)
  - Photo Unit #: C349? Earl Browder and officers of the 15th International Brigade, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1875A)
  - Photo Unit #: C350 Earl Browder[center] and officers of the 15th International Brigade, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1865)
  - Photo Unit #: C351 William Oderaka, Robert Minor, Anthony Drossel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0784)
  - Photo Unit #: C354 Edward Barsky (l.) and Edward Patterson, MacKenzie-Papineau, after Teruel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0785)
    (Moscow Number: 5/187/2)
  - Photo Unit #: C355 On the anniversary of their last year in Spain, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0786)
  - Photo Unit #: C357 After Teruel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0787)
  - Photo Unit #: C358 Morris Stamm (l.) and [?], Lincoln-Washington, after Teruel, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0788)
  - Photo Unit #: C360 Group of Californians in Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Agua-viva [?], Feb 1938 (Item 11-1021)
  - Photo Unit #: C363 Lillian Armstan, nurse, and Norman Dorland, 35th Division Sanidad [Health], Feb 1938 (Item 11-1022)
  - Photo Unit #: C365 Scene in front of Estado Mayor [Headquarters] at Cedrilla, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1023)
  - Photo Unit #: C366 Lincoln-Washington Battalion kitchen, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1024)
  - Photo Unit #: C367 Kitchen, Lincoln-Washington, Feb 1938 (Item 11-0378)
  - Photo Unit #: C368 Eating at Lincoln-Washington Battalion kitchen, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1025)
  - Photo Unit #: C369 Lincoln-Washington Battalion eating, Feb 1939 (Item 11-1026)
  - Photo Unit #: C370 Lincoln-Washington Battalion eating, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1027)
  - Photo Unit #: C371 Paul White of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1028)
  - Photo Unit #: C372 Soldiers of Lincoln-Washington Battalion, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1029)
  - Photo Unit #: C373 John Panaszewicz of Lincoln-Washington fortification group, John P. Hunter of Lincoln-Washington Chemical Unit, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1030)
  - Photo Unit #: C374 Anthony Kerhlicker, Elias (Ilya) Balagurchick, Lincoln-Washington fortification, Feb 1938 (Item 11-1031)
  - Photo Unit #: C380 Lincoln-Washington Battalion kitchen, Valverde, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1032)
  - Photo Unit #: C384 South American of Company 2, 59th Battalion, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1033)
  - Photo Unit #: C385 Machine-Gun group of Company 2, 59th Battalion, Mar 1938 (Item 11-1034)